SHUBHAM

Bachelor of Engineering(CSE)

+917696017079 ikshubham1@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/shubham-1045ba219/ Chandigarh

SUMMARY

I am an Engineering student pursuing my bachelor's degree in the computer science Engineering branch. I am always ready to learn new things and technologies. I know C++ and I have a basic understanding of Data Structures & Algorithm. I am also good in Frontend technologies like HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Reactjs and have a good knowledge of Backend technologies like Nodejs. I have a basic knowledge of computer fundamentals. I have one month internship experience with Block8, in MERN stack technology. I have good problem solving and debugging skills.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering (Computer Science Engineering)

Chandigarh College of Engineering and Technology, GPA 7.55/10

Intermediate/10+2

Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya, Percentage 79/100 2018 - 2019

Matriculation

Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya, GPA 9.0/10.0 2016 - 2017

EXPERIENCE

Intern Chandigarh Block8 07/2022 - 08/2022

- · Learned new technologies and implemented them.
- Helped other team members in debugging their code.
- Worked on the project (Leave Management System) using the MERN stack technology.
- Worked on both the Frontend and the Backend of the project.
- Project Repository: https://github.com/shubh045/leave-management-system

Remote **Open-Source Contributor** 09/2021 - 11/2021

Girlscript Winter of Contribution

- Contributed as a participant.
- Contributed in the form of documentation.
- Created documents on various topics of C/CPP and Web Development.
- Five pull requests got merged on GitHub.
- Contributions: HTML Button, Factorial using recursion, Fibonacci series using recursion, Matrix multiplication, Array as abstract datatype

PROJECTS

Al Image Generation Web App

02/2023 - 02/2023

2020 - 2024

A web app to generate images from textual description using the official DALL-E2 API

- Seamlessly integrated the DALL-E2 API into the project.
- Created a visually appealing user interface by taking ideas from the DALL-E2 website.
- Used Mongodb, Express, Reactis and Nodeis as technology stack.
- Explored and learned about generative AI, Reactjs and Nodejs.
- Project Repository: https://github.com/shubh045/dalle-clone

SKILLS

C++, HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQL, Reactis, Nodejs, MERN Stack, Git, Github

LANGUAGES

Hindi, English, Punjabi, Maithili